Thread Waxing Space (Gallery)
Archives of American Art, Smithsonian Institution
- Program Files, 1980s-2001, Series 1:; (Boxes 1-38; 35.7 linear feet)
  - "Beyond Ars Medica: Treasures from the Mutter Museum" (Nov. 19, 1995 - Jan. 11, 1996) (Box 14)
    - Correspondence, 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 30)
    - List of Artifacts, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 31)
    - Cards, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 32)
    - List of Photographs/Artworks, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 33)
    - Allan Ludwig Essay, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 34)
    - Mats for Photographs, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 35)
    - Catalog - Printing Quotes, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 36)
    - Shipping, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 37)
    - Loan Forms From Museum, 1995 (Box 14, Folder 38)
    - Panel Participants, 1995, (Includes 2 sound cassettes) (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - "Beyond Ars Medica: Treasures from the Mutter Museum" and Domenico de Clairo/Romain Pellas, Documentation (Nov. 19, 1995 - Jan. 11, 1996), 1995-1996 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Domenico de Clairo and Romain Pellas (Nov. 29, 1995 - Jan. 11, 1996), 1992-1996, (10 folders) (Box 14, Folder 41-50)
  - Domenico de Clairo and Romain Pellas (Nov. 29, 1995 - Jan. 11, 1996), 1992-1996, (4 folders; includes 1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 15, Folder 1-4)
  - Domenico de Clairo, Solstice Performance (Dec. 21-22, 1995), 1995 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Shawn Stewart Ruff and Chabliss Giobbi, "The Idealist: An Opera in Progress" (Jan. 16-27, 1996), 1995-1996, (2 folders) (Box 15, Folder 6-7)
  - "The News" [Inaugural Issue], 1996 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Dawn Dedeaux, "Free to Kill" (Feb. 8 - Mar. 16, 1996), 1992-1996, (4 folders) (Box 15, Folder 9-12)
  - Brett Cook-Dizney and Doug Argue (Feb. 8 - Mar. 12, 1996), 1994-1996, (5 folders) (Box 15, Folder 13-17)
  - "Offerings," Curated by Samantha Tsao (Mar. 29 - Apr. 27, 1996) (Box 15)
    - General, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 18)
    - Elena Berriolo, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 19)
    - John Corbin, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 20)
    - Peter Guthrie, 1994-1996 (Box 15, Folder 21)
    - Pieter Schoolwerth, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 22)
    - Elaine Tin Nyo, 1996, (Includes 2 computer discs: 3.5") (Box 15, Folder 23)
    - Christopher Whittey, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 24)
    - Ricardo Zulueta, 1996 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - "The Making of Painted Strokes: Incestuous" by Carter Kustera and Tiong Ang; "Offerings" Slides (Mar. 29 - Apr. 27, 1996), 1996 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - "The Making of Painted Strokes: Incestuous" by Carter Kustera and Tiong Ang (Mar. 29 - Apr. 27, 1996), 1992-1996, (7 folders; includes 1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 16, Folder 1-7)
  - New School Symposium, "Life, Sex and Death in the Digital Age" (Apr. 9-23, 1996), 1994-1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
  - SCRATCH Spring Benefit (May 2, 1996), 1996, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 9-11)
  - "Shred Sled Symposium," Curated by Aaron Rose (May 11 - June 15, 1996), 1995-1996, (9 folders) (Box 16, Folder 12-20)
  - "Shred Sled Symposium"and "Do You See What I See?" Photographic Materials (May 11 - June 15, 1996), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 21)
  - "Do You See What I See?" Curated by ABACA Students (May 11 - June 15, 1996), 1996, (2 folders) (Box 16, Folder 22-23)
  - The Kitchenette, ["Music in 12 Parts"], 1996 (Box 16, Folder 24)
  - Readers and Writers Festival (RAW)/Soho Arts Festival (May 17-19, 1996), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 25)
  - Kate Robin and Tim Cunningham, "Bride Stripped Bare" (June 22 - July 12, 1996), 1993-1996, (3 folders) (Box 16, Folder 26-28)
  - Jon Bepler and Sue Rees, "Incidents With Automatic Orchestra" (July 18-26, 1996), 1995-1996 (Box 16, Folder 29)
  - 3 Wave Benefit (July 31, 1996), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 30)
  - CMJ Music Festival (Sept. 4, 1996), 1996 (Box 16, Folder 31)
  - Henry Buhl, "Collection in Context" (Sept. 7 - Oct. 19, 1996), 1995-1998, (4 folders) (Box 16, Folder 32-35)
  - Henry Buhl, "Collection in Context" (Sept. 7 - Oct. 19, 1996), 1995-1998, (10 folders) (Box 17, Folder 1-10)
  - Anne Chadwick, "Vegetable House" (Sept. 7 - Oct. 19, 1996), 1996, (5 folders; includes 1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 17, Folder 11-15)
  - "Ambient Night" (Oct. 25, 1996), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 16)
  - Gail Gilbert, "An Unmeasurable Distance" (Oct. 26 - Nov. 3, 1996), 1996, (6 folders) (Box 17, Folder 17-22)
  - Election Night Vigil (Nov. 5, 1996), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 23)
  - "Famous in New York II" (Nov. 6, 1996) (Box 17)
    - Lou Acierno, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 24)
    - Dahn Hiuni, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 25)
    - Alyson Pou, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 26)
    - Artwork Documentation, 1996, (2 folders; includes 3 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 17, Folder 27-28)
    - Correspondence, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 29)
    - Press, 1996 (Box 17, Folder 30)
    - Card, 1993-1996 (Box 17, Folder 31)
  - Little Red School House Benefit (Nov. 7-10, 1996), 1996 (Box 17, Folder 32)
  - ST-X Ensemble Xenakis USA (Nov. 14, 1996), 1993-1997, (7 folders; includes 5 sound discs: CD) (Box 17, Folder 33-39)
  - Arturo Herrera and Carla Preiss (Nov. 21 - Dec. 21, 1996), 1993-1998, (7 folders) (Box 18, Folder 1-7)
  - Arturo Herrera and Carla Preiss; "Romper Room," Photographic Materials (Nov. 21 - Dec. 21, 1996), 1996 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - "Romper Room," Curated by Danielle Chang (Nov. 21 - Dec. 21, 1996) (Box 18)
    - Checklists, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Returns of Work, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Card, 1993-1996 (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Taro Chiezo, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - Catalog, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Gary Bachman, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - Press Release, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Press Lists, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Shipping, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble (Dec. 22, 1996), 1996, (6 folders; includes 1 sound disc: CD) (Box 18, Folder 18-23)
  - Ed Rath, "New Paintings" (Jan. 9 - Feb. 1, 1997), 1997, (6 folders) (Box 18, Folder 24-29)
  - The Kitchen Mailings, 1994-1995 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Kitchenette Season 1996/1997, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 31)
  - Kitchenette Miscellaneous Programming, 1995-1996 (Box 18, Folder 32)
  - Kitchenette Video, 1993-1995 (Box 18, Folder 33)
  - Ruth Kahn, "Want Drugs Want Food" (Jan. 9 - Feb. 1, 1997), 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 34)
  - "European Comics: Another Image" (Jan. 9 - Feb. 1, 1997) (Box 18)
    - Invoice to French Embassy, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 35)
    - Attendance, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 36)
    - Press Release - French Embassy, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 37)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 38)
    - Invitations, circa 1990s (Box 18, Folder 39)
    - Computer Rental, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 40)
    - Cardboard Furniture, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 41)
    - Photos of Washington, D.C., circa 1997 (Box 18, Folder 42)
    - Freight, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 43)
    - Film Festival, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 44)
    - Peter Kuper, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 45)
    - Howard Cruse, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 46)
    - Hotel, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 47)
    - GalleryBeat TeleVision, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 48)
    - Press, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 49)
    - Card and Slides, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 50)
    - TWS's Press Release, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 51)
    - Project Info, 1996 (Box 18, Folder 52)
    - Artist Info From Services Cultural, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 53)
    - Press Requests, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 54)
    - Press Kits, 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 55)
    - Art Spiegelman, 1997 (Box 18, Folder 56)
  - "Poets on Exhibit (Spoken Word)" (Feb. 6, 1997), 1996-1997, (6 folders) (Box 18, Folder 57-62)
  - Justin Bua (Feb. 20 - Mar. 15, 1997), 1997 (Box 18, Folder 63)
  - Erik Sanko, "We've Never Been Out of the House and We're All Doing Fine" (Feb. 20 - Mar. 15, 1997), 1997 (Box 18, Folder 64)
  - Marguerite Kahrl, "Magnetic Oracles" (Feb. 20 - Mar. 15, 1997), 1996-1997 (Box 18, Folder 65)
  - Photographic Materials for "Elsewhere," "Magnetic Oracle" (Marguerite Kahri), "We Never Leave" (Erik Sanko), and Justin Bua (Feb. 20 - Mar. 15, 1997), 1997 (Box 18, Folder 66)
  - Miami Arts Project, 1997-1998 (Box 18, Folder 67)
  - "Elsewhere" (Feb. 20 - Mar. 15, 1997), 1994-1997, (12 folders; includes 1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 19, Folder 1-12)
  - Memorial Service for Guillaume Gallozi (Mar. 23, 1997), 1997 (Box 19, Folder 13)
  - Patricia Winter, "The Buzzing of Insects and Body Check" (Apr. 3-5, 1997), 1996-1997, (5 folders) (Box 19, Folder 14-18)
  - "Drummin': A Work in Progress" (Apr. 26-27, 1997), 1996-1997, (14 folders; includes 1 videocassette: VHS) (Box 19, Folder 19-32)
  - Bingo Annual Benefit (May 2-3, 1997), 1997, (24 folders) (Box 19, Folder 33-56)
  - "Celluloid Cave," Curated by Dara Friedman (May 10 - July 2, 1997) (Box 20)
    - Slides, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - Possible Travel Venues/Budgets, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - Essay Questions and Responses - Lisa Young, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - General Info, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - Correspondence, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - Poster, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Mailing Lists, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Press, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Insurance Claim, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 9)
    - Press Info, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 10)
    - Attendance, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 11)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 12)
    - Marijke van Warmerdam, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 13)
    - Liisa Roberts, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 14)
    - Tacita Dean, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 15)
    - General Correspondence, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 16)
    - Rental Equipment, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 17)
    - Loan Agreements, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 18)
    - Installations, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 19)
    - Artists Bios, 1993-1997 (Box 20, Folder 20)
    - Xerox of Sign-In Book, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 21)
    - Venue Possibilities, 1994, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 22)
    - Video Recordings (May 10 - July 2, 1997), circa 1994, 1996, (2 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - The Builders Association, "Imperial Motel (Faust)", 1996, (2 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - "You Should Know Better," Curated by Samantha Tsao (May 10 - July 2, 1997), 1997 (Box 20)
    - Robert Beck, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 25)
    - Richard Erickson, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 26)
    - Card, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 27)
    - Christopher Verene, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 28)
    - Press Release, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 29)
    - Loan Forms, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 30)
    - Press, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 31)
    - Price Lists, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 32)
    - Checklists, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 33)
    - Correspondence, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - "Special Report on Roisin McAliskey" (June 4, 1997), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Mark Fox and Tony Luensman, "STAIN: Unconsummate Acts" (June 11-12, 1997), 1996-1997, (6 folders) (Box 20, Folder 36-41)
  - Charlotta Jenssen, "BrainThang" (June 13, 1997), 1997, (Includes 2 computer discs: 3.5") (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Minority Task Force on AIDS Benefit, "Hinds' Feet in High Places" (July 25, 1997), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - The School of Visual Arts MFA Photography Exhibition (July 28 - Aug. 15, 1997), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Downtown Arts Festival (Sept. 11-21, 1997), 1997 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - CMJ Music Festival (Sept. 3, 5, 1997), 1997, (3 folders) (Box 20, Folder 46-48)
  - "Ascent of Western Civilization," Curated by Michael Azerrad (Sept. 13 - Nov. 1, 1997), 1997 (Box 20)
    - Invitation and Slides, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 49)
    - Zine, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 50)
    - Press Release, 1997 (Box 20, Folder 51)
    - Correspondence with Michael Azerrad, circa 1980-1983, 1996-1997 (Box 20, Folder 52)
    - Press and Other, 1997-1998 (Box 20, Folder 53)
    - Ads, 1997, (Includes 3 computer discs: 3.5") (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - "Ascent of Western Civilization," Curated by Michael Azerrad (Sept. 13 - Nov. 1, 1997) (Box 21)
    - Video Info, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Book Info, 1996-1997 (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Working File: Artists, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Fugazi/MTV Video Release Fax, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Contracts, 1996 (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Video Lists From Exhibits, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Images for Website, 1997, (3 computer discs: 3.5") (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Advertising Specs, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Solicitation List and Letters, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - Zine Ads, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - Zine Draft, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Photographs - Nicholas McIntosh, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Photographs - Lindsay Brice, 1991, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Loan Agreements, 1997, (5 folders) (Box 21, Folder 14-18)
    - [Exhibition Materials?], 1980s-1990s, (Oversized materials housed in Box 38, Folder 3) (Box 21, Folder 19)
    - Video Recordings, 1997, (2 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 21, Folder 20)
    - Books, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 21)
    - Stephanie Chernikowski, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 22)
    - Original Notes, 1995-1997 (Box 21, Folder 23)
    - Listings, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 24)
    - Lindsay Brice, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 25)
    - Listening Station List, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 26)
    - Record Label Info, 1995-1997 (Box 21, Folder 27)
    - Correspondence with Michael Azerrad re: Artists, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 28)
    - Attendance, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 29)
    - Michael Azerrad's Mailing List, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 30)
    - Video, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 31)
    - Zines, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 32)
    - General, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 33)
    - Zine - General, 1997 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - "Mekons United" (Sept. 13 - Nov. 1, 1997), 1995-1997, (8 folders; includes 2 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 21, Folder 35-42)
  - Exit Art/The First World, "Public Notice" (Oct. 4 - Nov. 30, 1997), 1997 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - ArtStart's Benefit for Thread Waxing Space (Oct. 16, 1997), 1997 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - James Schneider, "Blue is Beautiful," "The Staticose Chamber" and "Oasis" (Oct. 30, 1997), 1997 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Maja (Nov. 1, 1997), 1997 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - S.E.M. Ensemble, "Many, Many Women" (Nov. 8, 1997), 1993-1997, (10 folders; includes 2 sound cassettes and 2 sound discs: CD) (Box 22, Folder 1-10)
  - Los Angeles Center for Photographic Studies (LACPS) Photo Arts Annual, 1996-1997 (Box 22, Folder 11)
  - "Famous in New York III" (Nov. 12, 1997), 1997, (8 folders) (Box 22, Folder 12-19)
  - Little Red School House Benefit and Exhibition (Nov. 13-16, 1997), 1997, (4 folders; oversized materials housed in Box 38, Folder 4) (Box 22, Folder 20-23)
  - The Builders Association, "Jump Cut (Faust)" (Dec. 3-20, 1997), 1996-1997, (26 folders) (Box 22, Folder 24-49)
  - "Lo-Fi Baroque," Curated by Michael Sarff and Carol Stakenas (Jan. 10 - Feb. 14, 1998), 1998, (15 folders) (Box 22, Folder 50-64)
  - "Love Songs, Nothing But Love Songs" (Feb. 14, 1998), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 65)
  - Threads of History (Jan. 10 - Feb. 14, 1998), 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 66)
  - Photographic Materials for "Looking Glass House" and "Lo-Fi Baroque" (Jan. 10 - Feb. 14, 1998), 1998 (Box 22, Folder 67)
  - Cadence Giersbach, "Looking Glass House" (Jan. 10 - Feb. 14, 1998), 1997-1998, (4 folders) (Box 22, Folder 68-71)
  - Union Settlement Junior Committee Benefit (Feb. 21, 1998), 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 72)
  - "Sanctuary: A Spiritual Music Festival"(Feb. 23-27, 1998) (Box 22)
    - Contracts, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 73)
    - Programs and Cards, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 74)
    - Reservations, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 75)
    - General, circa 1998 (Box 22, Folder 76)
    - Listings, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 77)
    - Pablo Iglesias, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 78)
    - Meeting Notes, 1997 (Box 22, Folder 79)
    - Keith Jones' Correspondence, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 80)
    - Tickets, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 81)
    - Press Release, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 82)
    - Press Clips, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 83)
    - Gospel - Dave Soldier Resume, 1996-circa 1998 (Box 22, Folder 84)
    - Miscellaneous, 1997-1998 (Box 22, Folder 85)
    - Institutional Radio Choir, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 86)
    - Emilio Barreto and Los Afortunados, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 87)
    - Gamelon Son of Lion, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 88)
    - The Danielson Family, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 89)
    - Reza DeRakshani, 1998, (Includes 1 sound cassette) (Box 22, Folder 90)
    - La Troupe Makandal, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 91)
    - Ancient Vibrations Groundation, 1998 (Box 22, Folder 92)
  - "Sanctuary: A Spiritual Music Festival" (Feb. 23-27, 1998) (Box 23)
    - Press, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Contacts, 1997-1998 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Installation, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Photographic Materials, 1998 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Sound and Video Recordings, 1998, (1 videocassette: VHS, and 1 sound cassette) (Box 23, Folder 5)
  - "Archigram: Experimental Architecture 1961-1974" (Mar. 12 - May 9, 1998), 1997-2000, (25 folders; includes 8 videocassettes: VHS, and 1 sound cassette) (Box 23, Folder 6-30)
  - "Archigram: Experimental Architecture 1961-1974," (Mar. 12 - May 9, 1998), 1997-2000, (47 folders) (Box 24, Folder 1-47)
  - "Spectacular Optical" (May 28 - July 2, 1998) (Box 24)
    - Description, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 48)
    - Publicity, 1998 (Box 24, Folder 49)
    - Possible Artists, 1997-1998 (Box 24, Folder 50)
    - Article by Lia Gangitano, circa 1998 (Box 24, Folder 51)
  - "Spectacular Optical" (May 28 - July 2, 1998) (Box 25)
    - Attendance, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Budget, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - MOCA Miami, Shipping, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Transart, circa 1998, (2 folders) (Box 25, Folder 4-5)
    - Packing Info, circa 1999 (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - CU Art Galleries, 1998-1999, (4 folders) (Box 25, Folder 7-10)
    - Return Shipping, 1999 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Checklist, circa 1998 (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Correspondence, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Krane Correspondence, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Haverford Systems, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Loans, 1998, (4 folders) (Box 25, Folder 16-19)
    - Passim, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 20)
    - Artist Contracts, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 21)
    - Lutz Bacher, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 22)
    - Jeremy Blake, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 23)
    - John Brattin, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 24)
    - Lygia Clark, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 25)
    - Bonnie Collura, 1998-1999 (Box 25, Folder 26)
    - Gregory Crewdson, 1995-1998 (Box 25, Folder 27)
    - Bryan Crockett, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 28)
    - Keith Edmir, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 29)
    - Jason Fox, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 30)
    - Julien Laverdiere, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 31)
    - Miranda Lichtenstein, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 32)
    - Charles Long, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 33)
    - Greg Lynn, 1997-1999 (Box 25, Folder 34)
    - Fabian Marcaccio, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 35)
    - Mariko Mori, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 36)
    - Tony Oursler, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 37)
    - Laura Parnes, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 38)
    - Randall Peacock, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 39)
    - Jose Antonio Hernandez Diez, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 40)
    - Alexis Rockman, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 41)
    - Alexander Ross, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 42)
    - Jana Sterbak, 1990-1998 (Box 25, Folder 43)
    - Shellburne Thurber, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 44)
    - Jane and Louise Wilson, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 45)
    - Luisa Lambri, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 46)
    - Fern Bayer, 1997-1998 (Box 25, Folder 47)
    - Photographic Materials, 1998 (Box 25, Folder 48)
  - "Spectacular Optical" (May 28 - July 2, 1998) (Box 26)
    - ("The Strange Objects of David Cronenberg's Desire"), 1997-1999, (5 folders) (Box 26, Folder 1-5)
    - Cinematheque Ontario, 1997 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Correspondence, 1997-1999, (2 folders) (Box 26, Folder 7-8)
    - Bios, circa 1997 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Tour Info, 1996-1999 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Listings, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - MOCA Miami, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - COCA, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - CU Art Galleries, 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - Museu de Arte Moderna do Rio de Janeiro re: Lygia Clark, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Catalog Printing Quotes, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Press Cuttings/Relevant Articles, circa 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Press Release, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - D.C. Interview, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 19)
    - Press, 1998-1999, (2 folders) (Box 26, Folder 20-21)
    - Advance Press, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 22)
    - Trans>, 1998, (Includes 1 sound disc: CD) (Box 26, Folder 23)
    - Copy of Guest Sign-In Book [CU Art Galleries?], circa 1998-1999 (Box 26, Folder 24)
    - Postcards, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 25)
    - Travel Kits, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 26)
    - MOCA Miami, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 27)
    - Fed Ex Declarations, 1998 (Box 26, Folder 28)
    - Video Recordings, 1990s, (3 folders; 9 videocassettes: VHS) (Box 26, Folder 29-31)
  - "Scout," Curated by Eileen Myles (June 2, 1998), 1998, (7 folders) (Box 26, Folder 32-38)
  - Third Wave Foundation Benefit (July 29, 1998), 1998 (Box 26, Folder 39)
  - "Beck & Al Hansen: Playing With Matches," Curated by Wayne Baerwaldt (Sept. 15 - Oct. 24, 1998), 1997-2000, (41 folders; includes 3 videodiscs: Mini-DV, and 1 sound cassette: DAT) (Box 27, Folder 1-41)
  - Virgil Marti, "Hot Tub" (Sept. 16 - Oct. 24, 1998), 1992-1998, (10 folders) (Box 27, Folder 42-51)
  - The Rotunda Gallery, "Interpreting" (Sept. 16 - Oct. 24, 1998), 1998 (Box 28, Folder 1)
  - "Scout," Curated by Eileen Myles (Oct. 6, 1998), 1998, (8 folders) (Box 28, Folder 2-9)
  - Primal Publishing, "Words & Moving Pictures" (Nov. 3, 1998), 1998, (4 folders) (Box 28, Folder 10-13)
  - CMJ Fall Music Festival (Nov. 4, 6-7, 1998), 1998, (6 folders; includes 1 sound disc: CD) (Box 28, Folder 14-19)
  - "The Failure to Assimilate: The Video Works of Cecilia Dougherty" (Nov. 13-15, 1998), 1998, (10 folders; includes 1 computer disc: 3.5") (Box 28, Folder 20-29)
  - "Message to Pretty," Curated by Lia Gangitano (Nov. 21 - Dec. 19, 1998) (Box 28)
    - Desk Binder Content, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 30)
    - Carrie Moyer, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 31)
    - Catalog, 1998, (Includes 1 computer disc: 3.5") (Box 28, Folder 32)
    - Shipping, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 33)
    - Listings, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 34)
    - Checklist, 1998-1999 (Box 28, Folder 35)
    - Invitations, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 36)
    - Enoc Perez, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 37)
    - Jens Fange, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 38)
    - Helen Sadler, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 39)
    - Sadie Benning, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 40)
    - Michael Lazarus, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 41)
    - Chris Kysor, 1997-1998 (Box 28, Folder 42)
    - Randy Wray, 1994, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 43)
    - Loan Agreements, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 44)
    - Installation Information, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 45)
    - [Catalog?], circa 1998, (Includes 1 computer disc: 3.5") (Box 28, Folder 46)
    - Photographic Materials, 1998 (Box 28, Folder 47)
  - Annelies Strba, "Shades of Time" (Nov. 21 - Dec. 23, 1998), 1997-1999, (8 folders) (Box 28, Folder 48-55)
  - Boaz Barkan, "Symptom" (Dec. 15, 1998), 1998, (4 folders) (Box 28, Folder 56-59)
  - Rafael Sanchez, "The Libation Bearers" (Jan. 8-10, 13-17, 1999), 1998-2001, (10 folders) (Box 28, Folder 60-69)
  - Barbara Pollack, "The Family of Men" (Jan. 28 - Mar. 6, 1999), 1998-2000, (3 folders) (Box 28, Folder 70-72)
  - Barbara Pollack, "The Family of Men" (Jan. 28 - Mar. 6, 1999), 1997-2000, (13 folders) (Box 29, Folder 1-13)
  - Luther Price, "Imitation of Life" (Jan. 28 - Mar. 6, 1999), 1998-2000, (11 folders) (Box 29, Folder 14-24)
  - Little Red School House Benefit Auction (Mar. 11-14, 1999), 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 25)
  - "Conceptual Art as Neurobiological Praxis," Curated by Warren Neidich (Mar. 25 - May 1, 1999) (Box 29)
    - Neidich NY Arts Interview, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 26)
    - Latest Proposal, Nov. 3, 1998, 1998 (Box 29, Folder 27)
    - Vinyl, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 28)
    - Warren's Notes on Steven Holl, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 29)
    - Card Text, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 30)
    - Installment Information, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 31)
    - Invitations, 1999 (Box 29, Folder 32)
    - General Info, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 33)
    - New School Info, 1998-1999 (Box 29, Folder 34)